Give me a second I,
I need to get my story straight
My friends are in the bathroom
Getting higher than the Empire State
My lover she's waiting for me
Just across the bar
My seat's been taken by some sunglasses
Asking about a scar and...
I know I gave it to you months ago
I know you're trying to forget
But between the drinks and saddle things
The holes in my apologies
You know, I'm trying hard to
take it back
So if by the time the bar closes
And you feel like falling down
I'll carry you home
Tonight,
We are young;
So let's set the world on fire,
we can burn brighter,
Than the sun
Tonight
We are young
So let's set the world on fire
We can burn brighter,
Than the sun
Now I know that I'm not
All that you got
I guess that I
I just thought maybe we could
find new ways to fall apart
But our friends are back
So let's raise a cup
Cause I found someone to carry me home
Tonight
We are young
So let's the set the world on fire
We can burn brighter
Than the sun
Tonight
We are young
So let's set the world on fire
We can burn brighter
Than the sun
Carry me home tonight
Just carry me home tonight
The world is on my side (
)
I have no reason to run (
(
So will someone come and carry
me home tonight
The angels never arrived(
But I can hear the choir (
n)
So will someone come and carry
me home
Tonight
We are young
So let's set the world on fire
We can burn brighter
Than the sun
Tonight
We are young
So let's set the world on fire
We can burn brighter
Than the sun
So, if by the time
the bar closes,
and you feel like falling down,
i'll carry you home,
Tonight
www.RentAnAdviser.com