Now and then I think of when
we were together
Like when you said you felt so
happy you could die
Told myself that you were right for me
But felt so lonely in your company
But that was love and it's an
ache I still remember
You can get addicted to a
certain kind of sadness
Like resignation to the end,
always the end
So when we found that we could
not make sense
Well you said that we would
still be friends
But I'll admit that I was glad
that it was over
But you didn't have to cut me off
Make out like it never
happened and that we were
nothing
And I don't even need your love
But you treat me like a
stranger and that feels so
rough
No you didn't have to stoop so low
Have your friends collect your
records and then change your
number
I guess that I don't need that though
Now you're just somebody that
I used to know
Now and then I think of all
the times you screwed me over
But had me believing it was
always something that I'd done
But I don't wanna live that way
Reading into every word you say
You said that you could let it go
And I wouldn't catch you hung
up on somebody that you used
to know
But you didn't have to cut me off
Make out like it never
happened and that we were
nothing
And I don't even need your love
But you treat me like a
stranger and that feels so
rough
No you didn't have to stoop so low
Have your friends collect your
records and then change your
number
I guess that I don't need that though
Now you're just somebody that
I used to know
Somebody
(I used to know)
(Now you're just somebody that
I used to know)
Somebody
(I used to know)
(Now you're just somebody that
I used to know)
(I used to know)
(That I used to know)
Somebody
www.RentAnAdviser.com